luxury-resort-bliss.com 2013-11-08

# About Us

I decided to make this page a sort of log of the progress of the website. Here are some of the lates benchmarks for the site.

December 2012 \- Baby and family are fine. great to have a job where I can work at home and spend time with baby.

 **Feb 2012** \- April and Ricky get a chance to explore some of Queenslands beauty spots on their Babymoon. 

| Monthly Statistics for February 2012  
---  
Total Visits|  **110075**  
Total Unique Visitors|  **72528**  
Total Pages|  **228321**  
  
 **June 2011** \- Ricky is able to finally stop work at a local hotel in[ Cairns](http://www.luxury-resort-bliss.com/cairns-resorts.html) ending a long on again , off again history of emplyment at Australian resorts, and  now work full time on the site giving the hard working April time for a well earned break.

 **September 2010** \- Ricky and April are able to resarch a little in Asia on their way down to Australia to live.

Monthly Statistics for September 2010  
---  
Total Visits|  **60767**  
Total Unique Visitors|  **31246**  
Total Pages|  **186525**  
  
 **June 2010** \- April and Ricky decide it's time to leave Korea (where they met) and spend some tome in Aprils parents basement writing and researching the site. Also some time is taken to do some travel and explore the U.S. and Canada. More quality affiliates are now comming on board now we are starting to get traffic.

Monthly Statistics for June 2010  
---  
Total Visits|  **68952**  
Total Unique Visitors|  **40621**  
Total Pages|  **187317**  
  
 **October 2007** \- The site is up and running and the first traffic begins to trickle in. We are keen to keep on working to deliver a better user experience and about this time Ricky quits his Spiritual website and dedicates more time to LRB (after work).

Monthly Statistics for October 2007  
---  
Total Visits|  **7**  
Total Unique Visitors|  **5**  
Total Pages|  **20**  
  
Feb 2006 - The website begins and we start to put together our list of the best websites in the world. Furious research and daily goals are set as we begin to make the site in between bouts of teaching English in Korea.

* * *

Luxury Resort Bliss is us: April and Ricky. We love travel and always get excited when writing about a new destination. We also love to find great travel deals. Here are our top travel partners and deals.  

Consider donating to [http://www.hollows.org.au](http://www.hollows.org.au/) along with your next vacation.  

Privacy Policy

 **What information do we collect?**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy..

 **Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

 **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

 **Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

 **Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our [privacy policy](http://www.freeprivacypolicy.com/).

This policy is powered by Free Privacy Policy and Rhino Support [help desk software](http://www.rhinosupport.com/).

Terms of use

While we do our best to keep our site updated, please ensure each booking is checked with the distributer before booking.
